(Sheldon:)...and at least one year
of algebraic topology?
Well, here come the jokes.
(Sheldon:)Why did the chicken
cross the Mobius strip?
To get to the same side?
Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)A neutron walks into a bar and asks,
"How much for a drink?"
(Sheldon:)The bartender says,
"For you, no charge."
(Sheldon:)Hello? I know you're out there.
(Sheldon:)I can hear you metabolizing oxygen
and expelling carbon dioxide.
It looks like we have some
academic dignitaries in the audience.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Randall
from the geology department...
(Sheldon:)...only man who's happy
when they take his work for granite.
Bada-cha.
(Sheldon:)I kid the geologists, of course...
...but it's only because
I have no respect for the field.
(Sheldon:)Let's get serious for a moment.